

## Graphic Design + Marketing Specialist

# Jenna Howard

- j.m.howard30@gmail.com
- Macon, GA
- jhoward.design
- **&** (478) 719-0474

#### **Profile**

With 10 years in digital & traditional design, I specialize in turning ideas into powerful visual content. My expertise includes brand awareness, visual storytelling, graphic design, & client engagement. I've served a range of clients, ensuring each brand's voice resonates with their target.

#### **Skills**

- Figma
- Active Campaign
- MailChimp
- Adobe Photoshop
- Facebook
- Adobe Illustrator
- Google Ads + Analytics
- Adobe PremierePro

## **Employment**

## 2020 - now Marketing Specialist at SPINEN

Collaborated with internal & client teams to craft visual assets for digital & print campaigns. Orchestrated email marketing initiatives that generated in excess of \$30,000 in revenue. Created custom client templates for most-used categories. Designed sales materials & internal training tools.

## 2019 - now Freelance Graphic Designer

Overhauled client branding & content planning across digital platforms including social media & Google Business. Developed & maintained client websites. Started mailing list for customer newsletters. Produced custom emails, brochures, menus, product photography, signage, & content. Reported & presented client analytics.

#### 2018 - 2019 Project Manager at Third Wave Digital

Administered projects for national & small business campaigns. Executed complex digital communications on behalf of key clients (e.g. 7-Eleven) including 3rd party vendors. Maintained a visual matrix of both content & format variations for menu boards across region, store types, & times of day for >200 stores.

#### Education

## 2011 - 2015 Georgia College & State University

Bachelor of Arts in Mass Communication